runescape.wiki 2019-04-03

# Privacy - Weird Gloop

> _Last modified:_ 20 September 2017

We’re committed to protecting the privacy of all of our users across our network, whether you are a reader or a contributor. As a result, we have a transparent, straight-forward privacy policy. By using any of the sites we operate, you are agreeing to our privacy policy and use of cookies.

### Information we collect

We collect information about users as they take part in certain activities on our network. Most notably, basic user information is collected during the registration of a new user account on any of our sites, which includes but is not limited to email addresses and full names. While using our sites, other demographic data such as gender and age may also be collected if the user chooses to disclose that information.

### Contributions

When you make a contribution to any of our sites, you are creating a permanent, public record of every piece of content added, removed, or altered by you. Public historical records will show when your contribution was made, as well as your username (if you are signed in) or your IP address (if you are not signed in). Any of this information is visible on the internet and can be found by search engines. Public contributions are associated with the user that contributed them and this information will be visible on the site.

### Automatically received data

When you requests a page on any of our sites, the web server automatically collects information about you, such as the your IP address, browser version and type, type and version of your operating system, the URL that referred you to this site, and in some cases the name of your internet service provider or mobile carrier. This data is used to provide a better experience for our users through determining ways to improve, administrate, and customise our site.

### Locally stored data

We actively collect some types of information with a variety of commonly-used technologies, which can include tracking pixels, JavaScript, our users’ local storage, and cookies. Depending on which technology we use, locally stored data can be anything from text and pictures, to personal information (like your IP address) and information about your use of our sites (like your username or the time of your visit). We use cookies to personalize your experience and retain preferences that you set. Some cookies that are in use are essential for our sites to function, including those that allow us to keep our users logged in for a duration of time.

We do not share personal information with companies, organisations, and indiduals outside of Weird Gloop unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * **If you give us consent**  
We may ask if you’d like to opt-in to share personal data with third parties. You’re welcome to say no, and we’ll adhere to your request.
  * **For legal reasons**  
We may share personal information with other companies and organisations if it is deemed necessary to: 
    * adhere to any law, regulation, or government request
    * enforce local and network-wide policies, including but not limited to our Terms of Use
    * detect and prevent security or technical issues
    * protect against harm to other users of our sites, or our company

We may share non-publicly identifiable information publicly and with our partners. Some non-identifiable information is collected by tools such as Google Analytics, which is subject to [Google’s partner privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

### Changes

Our privacy policy may change on occasion. Changes to the policy will be reflected on this page, and if there are significant changes, we will inform you via email if available.

### When this policy applies

This policy applies when viewing pages on any of our sites and using our services. It will not apply to any external links that are followed. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of sites that we link to.

### Storage duration

We keep any identifiable information we have for the shortest possible time, in accordance with law. Non-private information, such as contributions to the site, may be kept indefinitely subject to our licensing.
